# **Colton Keiser**

IT Audit Consultant // Python Developer

## Overview

Recent Information Sciences graduate, currently working as an IT Audit Consultant in St. Louis. Where I collaborate with clients to assess and improve the performance, compliance, and reliability of their IT systems.

Additionally, I serve on my firm's internal development team, where I design and build tools and applications for clients and internal use. I specialize in Python development and have experience with additional programming languages and frameworks, many of which are demonstrated in the projects on my portfolio website.

# **Experience**

IT Audit Consultant // Python Backend Developer, Protiviti | 2024-Present

- Perform client-facing IT audits, evaluating compliance and effectiveness of information systems and testing ITGC controls.
- Contribute to the internal programming team as a back-end developer, creating custom tools, applications, and process accelerators.

UIUC iSchool Advisor, UIUC iSchool | 2023-2024

- Provided tutoring for students in Information and Data Science programs. In Python and SQL related courses.
- Managed and updated the iSchool SharePoint website

Assistant Public Defender, Montgomery Courthouse | 2021

 Oversaw the management and updating of client records inside our internal database.

# **Contact**

Contact:

colton.dev02@gmail.c

OIII

Portfolio:

ckeiser2.github.io

### Education

University of Illinois, BS in Information Sciences | 2020-2024

Minor: Game Studies and Design

## Skills

Programming:

- Python
- C#
- SQL

Frameworks & Tools:

- LangchainFramework
- AzureDevelopment
- APIs

IT Infrastructure:

ITGC Testing